newsgarbage.com 2012-06-15

# newsgarbage | privacy policy

Our free and simple sign up allows you to vote on news, and submit stories. Why not give it a try! 

This Privacy Policy makes up one section of the Terms and Conditions of Use. Please read these Terms and Conditions of Use carefully and fully before using any of the Services provided by the site. By accessing this site or using any part of the content or services (both defined below) on the site, you agree to become bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to all of the Terms and conditions, you may not access the site or use any services or content on the site. newsgarbage acceptance is expressly conditioned upon your assent to all of these Terms and Conditions, to the exclusion of all other terms; If these Terms and Conditions are considered an offer by newsgarbage, acceptance if expressly limited to these terms.

newsgarbage respects and takes your privacy seriously. The information that you provide us with, or that is gathered automatically helps us and third parties to monitor our service and provide you with the services that you have subscribed to. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. If you have any concerns, questions or comments please email us. You can contact us through our Contact Us Page

Security

While we strive to keep the information that you supply directly or indirectly secure please be aware that the Internet is not a fully secure medium.

Registration

To use certain parts of the site we will ask you to register with us. As part of the registration process we ask for the following personally identifiable information:

1\. Email address.  
2\. Real Name.  
3\. Country of Residence.

While we DO NOT give our email lists out to other parties. We will only email you in the event of a change to the Terms and Conditions of Use, or in the event of a 3rd part informing newsgarbage that content you have submitted breaches their Intellectual Property Rights, see "Copyright and Intellectual Property Rights Notice".

Community Functions

We may make available to our users certain community functions, such as chat rooms, forums, message boards. Remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal, financial or other information. You use such community functions at your own risk.

NewsGarbage reserves the right to restrict access at will to users who are perceived as being detrimental to the community.

Cookies and other Short Term information

newsgarbage only use cookies to track your online presence at our website when you are logged in using our user login service. This does not store any personal information. If you object to us using cookies you should set your computer to block them, or access Your Account and choose No under the 'remember my login' option.

We also use tracking code, which determines the level of users and browsing patterns on the site in a 30 minute period. The information that is tracked is the following:

1\. IP Address.  
2\. Visited Page.  
3\. Time of Visit. 

Surveys

On occasion we may conduct online surveys. This is used to gauge our service, collect demographic information and other information that we may find useful. These surveys are of course optional.

Advertising

Our pages may occasionally carry advertising banners in one form or another. These are based on our own internal banner code and do not collect any information whatsoever about yourselves or set any cookies, the code is only there to track our banner views and clicks. newsgarbage DOES NOT ever carry any popup banners in any form. If you wish to advertise on newsgarbage, please email us. You can contact us through our Contact Us Page

Usage of Information

If requested we may submit your information to local or government authorities or if we determine that it is necessary to so to comply with applicable laws, to protect the interests and safety of another company or the interests and safety of other visitors to the site.

Policy Changes

By using our site you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware and accept that our policy may change with time. Any changes to this policy will appear on this page.
